{"questions":[{"question":"As part of AGILE programming, must you always have a prototype ready at the end of a cycle?","level":1,"answers":["Yes","No"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":0},{"question":"What is the SOA principle which allows running services on different devices?","level":3,"answers":["Loose Coupling","Reusability","Interoperability"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Which of the following is not a design pattern?","level":2,"answers":["Comparative","Strategy","Adapter","State"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":0},{"question":"Which is not a maintenance risk?","level":2,"answers":["Schedule","Low Quality","Standardization","Loss of Control"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Which is not a type of maintenance?","level":2,"answers":["Corrective","commutative","Adaptive","Perfective"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":1},{"question":"What is not a scrum role?","level":1,"answers":["Product owner","scrum master","Customer","developer"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Is \"The system will perform a maintenance every saturday between 4am and 6am\"\na functional requirement?","level":1,"answers":["Yes","No"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":1},{"question":"In white box testing - is the software structure known?","level":1,"answers":["YES","NO"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":0},{"question":"Will 100% Path coverage imply 100% Branch Coverage?","level":2,"answers":["Yes","No"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":0},{"question":"We will use a private cloud:","level":1,"answers":["in case of sensitive data","in any situation","for public data"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":0},{"question":"Which Design Pattern allows only one appearance of each object?","level":1,"answers":["Factory","Singleton","Memento"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":1},{"question":"A system will repsond within 2 seconds of a button click is what type of requirement?","level":1,"answers":["Functional","Non-Functional","None of the above"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":1},{"question":"Is it recommended to work with multiple standards at the same time?","level":2,"answers":["Absolutely not","Always","Depends on the company's needs"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":2},{"question":"ISO 90003 focuses on","level":3,"answers":["Product management","people management","quality management"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Graphical Notation is:","level":2,"answers":["a UML Example","fits programmers only","Solves the ambiguousness problem"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":0},{"question":"Traceability is:","level":3,"answers":["Consistency of users","Consistency of code","Consistency of requirements"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":2},{"question":"What is correct about SAAS PAAS?","level":3,"answers":["SAAS is used by developers","paas is used by servers and communication","paas is used by developers"],"team":"Viper","correct_ans":2}]}